Ms. Tracy Janeel Ramsumairsingh

Lp 4 San Pablo Trace,

Valencia.

Ph. 718-8483

Email: janeel\_business@yahoo.com

The Human Resources Department,

Dear Madam,

I am applying for a position in commensuration with my qualifications and experience. The ingenuity and fervor I would bring to such a position would be of prodigious interest and benefit to our venerated establishment.

My creativity, superb inter-personal skills, assiduous nature and proficiency of execution of a given task, emphasize my suitability for the position I am requesting you entrust me.

I have enclosed a copy of my resume for your critic; it is my fervent belief that no letter can articulate an individual's talent. I am confident that an interview would be of relevance to both me and your organization at your convenience evidently.

Yours Respectfully,

*Tirsingh*Ms. Tracy J. Ramsumairsingh

## **Biographical Data:**

DoB: 14<sup>th</sup> June, 1984 Phone: 868-718-8483 : 868-376-7712

E-mail: janeel\_business@yahoo.com

Address: San Pablo Trace,

Valencia. Trinidad W.I.

### **Objective:**

I wish to be given the opportunity to flourish at your venerated establishment with the prospect of advancement.

### **Education:**

Currently

School of Business and Computer Science

Foundation in Accountancy

FA1

MA1

FA2

MA2

#### Currently

Alison

Business Communication - Fundamentals of Business Writing (90%)

Introduction to Spanish (80%)

Introduction to Time Management (92%)

Introduction to Marketing (80%)

Diploma in Customer Service (84%)

Diploma in Nursing and Patient Care (83%)

Back Care and Manual Handling (Theory) (100%)

Introduction to Conversational English (91%)

Introducing the Art of Negotiation (86%)

How to Plan Your Career Path (100%)

Fundamentals of Business Law (87%)

Leadership Skills in Business (90%)

Customer Service Training (90%)

Adobe Photoshop (100%)

Fundamentals of Human Resources (95%)

Fundamentals of Biology (85%)

Back Safety (93%)

Introduction to Strategic Management (84%)

Introduction to Service Management (80%)

Introduction to Change Management (80%)

Modern Human Resource Management - Recruitment and Selection Process (83%)

Applied Psychology - Matching Marketing Strategies to Consumer Personalities (88%)

Applied Psychology - Introduction to Consumer Behavior (95%)

Introduction to Immunology (80%)

Employer - Employee Law (90%)
Introducing the Art of Negotiation (86%)
Leadership Skills in Business (90%)
Advanced Biology 1 (100%)
Fundamentals of Accounting (94%)
Marketing Success for your Business (90%)

## 2017

First Aid For Free
Basic First Aid (Pass)
Advanced First Aid (Pass)
Pediatric First Aid (Pass)
Defibrillation Training (Pass)

## 2011

SITAL College L.C.C.I. Diploma in Advertising, Marketing and Public Relations Advertising (ungraded) Marketing (Pass) Public Relations (Pass)

#### 2009

Harvest Time Vocational Center Principles of Business (CXC) (3)

#### 2002

Arima Senior Comprehensive Mathematics (CXC) (3) English (CXC) (1) Human & Social Biology (CXC) (C) Dressmaking & Design (CXC) (B) English Literature (CXC) (4)

## **Work Experience**

Currently
Optometrists Today
Marketing Assistant
#1B Optics House, Frederick Street,
Port of Spain
623-2329

09- September-2015—14-January-2016 Unit One Security Limited Marketing Manager #25 Corner 7th Street & 8th Avenue Barataria 222-3438

01-December-2009— 11-September-2015 School of Business & Computer Science Ltd Accounting Associate 1 (Receivables) # 53-54 Sagan Drive, Champs Fleurs 663-7227

17-June-2013—17-May-2014 Digicel Ansa Building, Maraval Road, Port of Spain 399-9999

Trinidad Broadcasting Company 15-July-2008 - 30-April-2009 Announcer/Operator St. Vincent Street Port of Spain. 623-9797

#### **Volunteer Work**

I worked as a tutor for a summer camp for a number of years until I started working full time.

#### References

Reverend Cheryl Sylvester # 26-27 Charlotte Street, Port of Spain 271-8097

Kurt Williams Trinidad Broadcasting St Vincent Street, Port of Spain 623-9801

Kevin Ruiz School of Business and Computer Science #53-54 Sagan Drive, Champs Fluers 663-7227

### **Hobbies**

I enjoy Reading, new challenges, writing, swimming, singing, trying new exotic foods and meeting new people.

### **Computer Skills**

2001

**Computer Literacy**